dealfuel.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy | DealFuel - DealFuel

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.
  * You have the option to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  ??Alternatively you can opt out – opt out of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on **31 Jan 2012**

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
